businessfinancestore.com 2013-12-20

# Privacy Policy | Business Finance Store

## THE BUSINESS FINANCE STORE’S PRIVACY POLICY – A COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY

This site is owned and operated by The Business Finance Store. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At The Business Finance Store, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

### INFORMATION THE BUSINESS FINANCE STORE GATHERS AND TRACKS

The Business Finance Store gathers two types of information about users:  
Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to participate in our blogging site, to participate in our message boards or forums, or to gain additional information about our products and services.

Information The Business Finance Store gathers through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers’ needs and to help our Marketing Division better understand the demographics of our audience. Because The Business Finance Store derives its revenue mainly from the sales of its service packages your personal information will never be given to a third party unless the third party is a direct affiliate of The Business Finance Store and part of the processing team.

The Business Finance Store Gathers User Information In The Following Processes:

#### Optional Voluntary Information

We offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:

  * Blogging  
Users of the site’s blogging platform must register separately for these services (free of charge) in order to post blogs, although they needn’t register to visit the site. During registration the user is required to choose a username, create a password, add an email address, agree to the Terms of Service, and choose whether they want a blogging website or just a user account.
  * Electronic newsletters policy (Dispatches)  
We may offer a free electronic newsletter to users in the near future. The Business Finance Store gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily open an account (i.e. a blog or username). Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management page. Users can also subscribe to the newsletters with any customer service representative or by emailing The Business Finance Store at info@BusinessFinanceStore.com.
  * Surveys  
The Business Finance Store may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our affiliated partners. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.

#### Children

Consistent with the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.  
Usage trackingThe Business Finance Store tracks user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. The Business Finance Store does break down overall usage statistics according to a user’s domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user’s browser).

The Business Finance Store uses tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

#### Cookies

We may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. The Business Finance Store uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you’ve set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in message boards, forums, polling and surveys.

### USE OF INFORMATION

The Business Finance Store uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in surveys, and blogs. We may send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule, and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. The Business Finance Store never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don’t like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don’t track which terms a particular user enters.

The Business Finance Store creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for our own internal use. We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

### SHARING OF THE INFORMATION

The Business Finance Store uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help us understand the demographics of our clients. This is essential to keeping our service free. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

### SECURITY

The Business Finance Store operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers.

### OPT-OUT POLICY

We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:

  * Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters.
  * Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas such as the blog site, however opting out does not change the collection of personal data. The personal data collected is necessary in order to make any payouts.

### YOUR CONSENT

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by The Business Finance Store. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
